<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type = "text/xsl" href = "Task2.xsl"?>
<root>
    <str1>
        O my Luve's like a red, red rose,
        That's newly sprung in June:
        O my Luve's like the melodie,
        That's sweetly play'd in tune.
        
        As fair art thou, my bonie lass,
        So deep in luve am I;
        And I will luve thee still, my dear,
        Till a' the seas gang dry.
        
        Till a' the seas gang dry, my dear,
        And the rocks melt wi' the sun;
        And I will luve thee still, my dear,
        While the sands o' life shall run.
        
        And fare-thee-weel, my only Luve!
        And fare-thee-weel, a while!
        And I will come again, my Luve,
        Tho' 'twere ten thousand mile! 
    </str1>
    <str2>
        Robert Burns (25 January 1759 – 21 July 1796) (also known as Rabbie Burns, Scotland's favourite son, the Ploughman Poet, the Bard of Ayrshire and in Scotland as simply The Bard[1][2]) was a poet and a lyricist. He is widely regarded as the national poet of Scotland, and is celebrated worldwide. He is the best known of the poets who have written in the Scots language, although much of his writing is also in English and a 'light' Scots dialect, accessible to an audience beyond Scotland. He also wrote in standard English, and in these pieces, his political or civil commentary is often at its most blunt.        
        He is regarded as a pioneer of the Romantic movement and after his death became a great source of inspiration to the founders of both liberalism and socialism. A cultural icon in Scotland and among the Scottish Diaspora around the world, celebration of his life and work became almost a national charismatic cult during the 19th and 20th centuries, and his influence has long been strong on Scottish literature.
    </str2>
    <str3>
        Born 	25 January 1759
        Alloway, Ayrshire, Scotland
        Died 	21 July 1796 (aged 37)
        Dumfries, Scotland
    </str3>
    <str4>
        "The Crocodile"   	
               
        Today I saw a crocodile,
        It sat and stared at me!
        I didn't run, I didn't shriek,
        In case I was his tea!
        
        No move I saw the snapper make,
        His jaws remained tight shut.
        Whilst sweat poured down my forehead,
        I heard rumbles from his gut!
        
        I've been in worse predicaments,
        But only in my head.
        Like wrestling with big brown bears,
        And monsters from our shed!
        
        But feeling brave I shuffled close,
        To see his scary jaws.
        The crocodile was not impressed,
        And flexed his giant claws!
        
        The beast prepared to eat me up,
        He snapped, he snarled, he blew!
        But I just stood and tapped the glass,
        'Cause this croc is in the zoo!
        
        ©2003 Gareth Lancaster        
    </str4>
</root>